## **Curriculum Vitae of Cameron Jordan Sheosunker**



### **Details**

I.D Number : 0005175122083
Nationality : South African
Race : Indian

Sex : Male
Marital Status : Single
Driver's License : Code 8

Address : 19 Second Street Hillary, Durban, 4094

Contact Number : 071 873 3907

Email Address : cameronjsheosunker17@gmail.com

#### **About Me**

I am a B.Sc. in Information Technology Graduate.

I have completed my studies at North West University and I am very grateful that I was given the opportunity and also very honoured to have passed with distinction. My university experience has been challenging, I have gained a lot of knowledge during these past three years and have had my fair share of ups and downs. I am currently trying to broaden my understanding on information security as a whole and would love the opportunity to enhance my skillset.

I am a quick and fast learner who can absorb new information effectively and can communicate clearly. I possess good bonding skills and have an inquiring mind that is eager to broaden my knowledge and grow as an individual. I have a fascination with building websites from scratch, database management systems, general applications and cybersecurity, and I always strive for a high degree in accuracy and attention to detail.

My current interests are in video games, I love modifying games, currently trying to create some of my own mods and scripts. I find artificial intelligence fascinating and the idea of allowing machines to "think for themselves".

I like fishing, because even if I don't catch anything, its' still very relaxing and peaceful if no one steals my fishing spot. Finally, I enjoy socializing & traveling, as I am always eager to make new friendships along the way. Overall, I am passionate about technology and I would love to be given the opportunity to learn more about it.

## **Work History**

#### Administrator Clerk, CLS Brokers; 2018 - 2020

CLS Brokers is an approved financial services provider where I worked as an administrator, handling client queries, quotations and filing. I have learnt many skills throughout my employment such as good communication and listening skills, reporting and problem solving.

For a project for one of my modules, I had to create a database management system for a business. I decided to use CLS Brokers as inspiration for the project. This system was written in C# using Visual Studio.

### Cybersecurity Intern, Altron Bytes People Solutions; 2021 - 2022

I am currently a part of a cybersecurity internship for one year that started in May 2021. I have learned many aspects related to cloud computing and security such as configuration and deployment of cloud models, security, maintenance, management and troubleshooting. My current objectives are to monitor a SIEM, patch and security patch management, EDR monitoring, installing/configuring applications on user devices and reporting.

## **Education**

### 1. Kharwastan Secondary School

#### Subjects:

- English, Afrikaans, Life Orientation, Mathematics, Physical Science, Information Technology
- & Geography. <u>Duration</u>: 2012 - 2017

# 2. North West University

Qualification: B.Sc. IT Duration: 2018 – 2020

## **Skills**

#### Hardware:

Maintenance, Peripherals, Drivers and Troubleshooting

#### Software:

- Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Projects and Access)
- Visual Studio and Visual Studio Code
- QM for Windows
- N-Central
- SentinelOne
- Autotask
- Security Information and Event Management (SIEM)
- CyberCNS

## **Certifications:**

- CompTIA Cloud+
- CompTIA Security+
- CompTIA Secure Cloud Professional

#### **Programming Languages:**

- Python
- C#
- C++
- (
- JAVA
- VB.NET

- ASP.NET MVC
- HTML, CSS & JavaScript
- SQL

# **Achievements**

- Created a responsive CV/Resume Website using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. https://cameronjsheo.github.io/CV/
- Created a website with a database management system in asp.net MVC Core. This site is no longer functioning since I hosted it on Azure using a free trial.
- Created a SIEM Guide website using HTML, CSS and JavaScript, which greatly improved the teams effectiveness and understanding of events.
- Created a digital solution in C# for a theoretical business, going fully in depth with the system development life cycle and project documentation.

Thank you for taking the time to review my CV. I hope to hear from you soon!